[
    {
        "question": "die Katze, die Katzen",
        "answer": "Macska",
        "interval": 2,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "Cats"
    },
    {
        "question": "Macska",
        "answer": "die Katze, die Katzen",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "Cats"
    },
    {
        "question": "r Hund -e",
        "answer": "Kutya",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "e Blume -n",
        "answer": "Virág",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "s Haus -er",
        "answer": "Ház",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Macska",
        "answer": "e Katze -n",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kutya",
        "answer": "r Hund -e",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Virág",
        "answer": "e Blume -n",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ház",
        "answer": "s Haus -er",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Iskola",
        "answer": "e Schule -n",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Asztal",
        "answer": "r Tisch -e",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ajtó",
        "answer": "e Tür -en",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Szék",
        "answer": "r Stuhl -e",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Könyv",
        "answer": "s Buch -er",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lámpa",
        "answer": "e Lampe -n",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "e Schule -n",
        "answer": "Iskola",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "r Tisch -e",
        "answer": "Asztal",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "e Tür -en",
        "answer": "Ajtó",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "r Stuhl -e",
        "answer": "Szék",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "s Buch -er",
        "answer": "Könyv",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "e Lampe -n",
        "answer": "Lámpa",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    },
    {
        "question": "e Katze -n",
        "answer": "Macska",
        "interval": 1,
        "last_review": "2024-12-05",
        "score": 0,
        "category": "TestData"
    }
]